Roberto Rob bet though that Gonzalez I'm
a man of many names a man of many names
man the owner of a vie clothing I'm
finally I'm pumped to finally be in the
podcast brother me too I'm glad to be
here I love sharing my story yeah dude
it's great to hear I feel like every
time customers come in and they get to
talk to you or talk to one of your
employees that knows what's going on
here they instantly benefit they're like
of course I wanted to support this
company so it's just cool I want to
bring up immediately if you think about
it when you first started like I would
be throwing illegal outdoor raves in the
woods and you would be selling this
company out of your trunk of your outie
so when I had like four designs - yeah
right well did everybody was happy to
rep you because everybody always really
liked what you stood for I feel like
your personality definitely communicates
really well in your clothing you know
and that's you know that's why you've
done so well so people are like they
would they want to support you of course
they love the designs - but yeah if you
want to just start with so like if you
have a little bit of your background as
a person as it relates to AI clothing so
you know let's just say the next few
minutes let's get to know the founder of
high clothing looks like nothing about
and what's what's bet though about yes
started when I was younger you know
remember my mom took e son tucking us
into bed and just letting us know
planting the seed into our mind letting
us know like hey whatever you put into
your mind you can create absolutely you
know and at a young age I always knew I
wanted to be like entrepreneur but I
wanted to be more than just an
entrepreneur I wanted to help people
mm-hmm growing up I always was trying to
help my mom in any way I could she'd be
washing the dishes and I'd be like can I
can I help you you know I want to help
you or if she'd be sweeping beer can I
do that I want to be I want to be able
to help you yeah so yeah naturally I
wanted to help people and then as I
started getting older like I was never
the type of person to like go out and
like hustle stuff you know that wasn't
that wasn't in my blood at the beginning
you know but I did have a vision
of wanting to be my own boss and not
having to work for the man but not only
that I wanted to be able to do something
so that I can help humanity and that
vision grew bigger as I started getting
older and I was able to continue to
teach myself things you know it's around
the time that I got into high school is
when I feel like the vision really grew
because because you taught yourself like
design and stuff right yeah yes so I
remember sitting and like this was like
my senior year and sitting in class and
creating stuff on the art app that they
have you know on the computer I remember
so much stuff for that matter then but
now you BIC this is so you can't do
anything with it yeah exactly and that's
the thing there was there was so much
limits to that but I didn't allow that
to limit myself I was like I got to
figure out how to create stuff yeah
you're still able to color outside those
lines exactly and the cool thing is like
nowadays when people are like oh I
remember what I used to sit next to you
in class and this is what you were doing
you know now you got two stores and you
continue you continue to grow yeah so
you know very humbling the kid with the
doodle in a dream yeah yeah so and
that's the thing like I started my
senior year with like 12 credits you
needed 20 to graduate geez so I was
pretty much a sophomore you know I hated
school I miss school wasn't for me you
know yeah I think a lot of school that
way during school and that's the thing
school is just uh it's there to make you
a worker mm-hmm that's what schools for
you know yeah some people do really well
in school and some people just feel like
it's slowing them down because they're
like I'm not gonna use any of this stuff
but I mean it does really come full
circle like a lot of stuff you get
taught in school at the moment you're
like this sucks I don't want to be I
would rather be creating clothing but
there's some of it where you're like oh
I'm glad I learned that right exactly
and my senior year was a big learning
curve for me because I was like dang
like I need to catch up to everyone like
I'm Way behind you know so
I was just thinking to myself like how
am I gonna do this he knows so on top of
like creating stuff and like wanting to
continue to grow that dream like I had
to fulfill another vision and you gotta
get it together and make sure you
graduate exactly fulfilling the vision
of like I I'm gonna walk with my class
I'm not gonna disappoint my mom and my
brothers of course I'm the oldest out of
three yeah they're looking up to you
exactly so I had to set the picture
straight so what you did oh gosh you get
all those credits yeah graduates yeah I
graduated it's great and I walked with
my class and like that right there
taught me that like you know whatever
you put you know again my mom's voice
came into my head like whatever you put
your mind to you can create yeah and I
visioned myself walking with the class
and I just I'm like my number one fuel
was my mom yeah cuz I didn't want to let
her down of course I was like I'm not
gonna let my mom down like I'm like her
first child like you know this is a big
thing for and for me for me to
disappoint her would've hurt me more
than it would have probably hurt her
absolute you know so I think a lot of us
at a young age we can get to that point
where it's like oh I maybe I was being a
little selfish and not like I was you
know effing off not paying attention my
grades my give me and something to other
people besides just ourselves a lot of
the times that's good that you're
recognizing that so you graduated and
you still kept doing it you still kept I
clothing when did when did I clothing
like you printed your first shirt when
is that once the jump between graduation
this so so I got the idea my senior year
oh sorry
get back to it you know like we kind of
went off of like you know
oh no this doesn't thing so that's my
job to just bring it right back around
to because I do the same thing yeah okay
back to senior year so there was a group
of individuals who started their own
clothing company I remember going to
school and like everyone rocking their
stuff I'm like well I'm like that's
dough like I want to do that yeah
exactly they planted another seed into
my mind they planted a seed into my mind
and I was like you can literally start
something from nothing isn't that such a
revelatory
thing you know it's so great that you
took that and you're like oh instead of
being like a hater right instead of Jack
they did that and I wish I could do that
and their sucks in my sector you're like
bro that's wonderful that's great we
let's I could do that too you know use
it yeah how do I do that because I won't
get easily inspired as well yeah no
doubt
so as soon as I saw that you know that
was a possible thing you know because
coming from Longview you know you don't
really have inspiration to be more than
what this town has for you right yeah
that's what holds this a lot of holds a
lot of us back of continuing to grow
into who we want to be one day and then
cuz with like the people around you and
then you know your family is a big one
too but yeah we're definitely an
old-fashioned small town I mean we're
yeah we're in between Seattle and
Portland but we're we're ten years
behind them with a lot of stuff we're
with a lot of exactly well the dream
here is to work at the mill you get the
you make the most money there and you
know you can provide for your family and
that's good enough you know but I wasn't
looking for good enough right that's the
thing as so many like we out we have
tons of friends who do that and they do
well and they have wonderful lives but
they just as much as we no no nothing
all they know just much we know though
that like we could be like hey bro could
you picture me doing that and they're
like absolutely not
they're like bro I you've always been
doodling you need to keep dueling
whatever you can do so it works for some
people but there's so many people who
you know if you're high school right now
listening to this and you're just
itching because you're just like man I
don't know I don't I don't want that
life I don't want the you know the
middle life the office life whatever you
can just keep keep total in man and keep
doodling and keep like having
perseverance and keep you know building
into what this is so keep creating yeah
exactly keep thinking big because
thinking big is what gets you to that
next level yeah obviously taking action
is a big big part of it too so yeah so
so you took action so you had so so yeah
the idea from them so like they have a
clothing company like [__] I could do
this too you know what
and then as soon as I started thinking
about that I'm like I'm gonna go to
Google University and low
how do you start a clothing company oh
yeah so there was like five major things
that came up and the one thing that
stuck out to me was what's going to make
you different and why are people gonna
want to support you hmm okay and then
that one really stuck with me so when I
was thinking of the company it was like
what is it gonna be called you know you
gotta have a cool name at least yeah but
that's the thing like the more I thought
of it the more signs started coming to
me and letting me know like hey this is
it
so whenever I'd be sitting around
watching TV and I was thinking about it
a night commercial would pop up like oh
okay
you know whenever I'd be talking to my
friends about it and I'd hop on my phone
like cool pictures of eyes would pop up
and then the I the word I did you know
like at this point you're like maybe I'm
gonna call I clothing like what's that
or I'm just noticing eyes I was just
noticing the whole eye thing well that's
and then like that's the word the word I
would pop up everywhere and then I
caught on to that you know because it's
all about catching onto an opportunity
when it's here
yeah and duty and my dancers were tuned
to it exactly exactly so I was like okay
I'm like I clothing company I was like
okay I'm like that's pretty cool I'm
like but again that third question of
like what's gonna make you different
mm-hmm
that one came up and I was like okay so
we got a cool name kind of but what's
what's so cool about it you know people
aren't just gonna want a support eye
clothing company it just because it's
something they know exactly you know so
from there I'm like oh I thought of the
company DGK you know it already got okay
yeah they had a guy they had an acronym
that said dirty ghetto kids and I was
like I mean I used to have some of their
stuff but like I never really understood
what dirty ghetto kids met and in my my
nose like these guys have made a lot of
money
you know and impacted a lot of people
with this dirty ghetto kids acronym yeah
and you're like so what's that
represented exactly exactly cuz I didn't
know so like in my mind I'm like alright
well I'm gonna come up with an acronym
that's positive hell yeah and I want
this to spark people's minds to start
thinking differently you know and I want
to make sure everyone who supports us
knows what it is it's not just a cool
t-shirt a cool graphic that you're
wearing
and as essence exactly so I look alright
I was gonna be an acronym so from there
I'm like what's the first letter gonna
be and immediately the the word urn came
to my mind right away because the way
that I was raised is my parents never
gave me anything unless you know I
earned it if I wanted something they'd
be like alright go mow the lawn you know
or go wash the dishes go pull weeds you
know so urn came to me easily just
because that that's been my life you
know yeah you don't get anything handed
to you unless you do something for it
right and then the Y came to me because
it had to be about you you know the
customer your journey to excellence and
becoming a better version of yourself so
I got earned EUR and then I didn't know
what the lassie was gonna be and then I
was reading a book and the word
excellence like bowled it out
yeah I was just like excellence and then
I went to my journal and I was like
earning your Excellencies aful and I was
like whoa we just brought I found right
like you did you sit back you just saw
it earn your excellence written out
there right yeah and I was just like
whoa I'm like this is it I'm like I
clothing company earn your excellence
like this flows yeah it does I'm like
this blows and this this goes and then
around that time like I said and I still
didn't understand the full meaning of
earning your excellence until one day I
was down at Washington Square and I was
walking around with some friends and
this dude and a kiosk comes up to me
he's like hey man he's like I got a
question for you
like what's up he's like do you know
what you want to do with your life and
I'm like I know exactly what I want to
do with my life he's like really and
then I just gave him the whole spiel of
like you know what I'm doing and what my
plans are for the future he's like wow
he's like you really do know what you
want to do with your life did you know
at that point that you knew what you
wanted to do like yeah you realize what
you're gonna say so you were saying it
yeah oh good okay well I've been
thinking about like so this is probably
like six six eight months and they're
like all right already up i clothing
company this is what i want to do with
it is this right after high school or
sister yeah this is after high school
yeah
so 18 yeah exactly 18 I'm like oh yeah I
already know what I want to do so I gave
him the whole spiel and he's like wow
okay and this dude was a recruiter for a
college so that's how he was asking me
do you know what you want to do with
your life because it was for like dental
and that's the thing before like I
graduated like that's what I wanted to
do I wanted to become a dentist so I was
kind of like interested in what he had
to say but then right before I had left
he's okay he's like I want you to read
this book and I'm like okay and I hated
reading you know school kind of teaches
you to not like reading you throw that
whole annotation over that negative
exactly you're like oh because they're
forcing excuse me they're forcing you to
read right you know I don't like you
obviously you're not gonna enjoy it if
you're being forced and if it's not
subjects that you really like yeah and
if you're not into it you're just gonna
be like all right this is stupid like I
never want to touch a book getting
anybody in this world hey would you like
to learn about something that you don't
care about Oh No thank you and then
instead they're like every kid you do
that though I mean I guess there is some
stuff we need to learn but anyway so
yeah after high school you what was this
book he gave you so yeah the name of the
book was the slide edge by Jeff Wilson
and I haven't actually heard of that one
and this book talks about the compound
effect okay and you know earning your
excellence is the compound effect okay
so the compound effect is all about
being conscious of what you're doing
because it's little things that we're
doing every day that are adding up to
the lifes we're going to be living one
day you know so let's just say you go to
Jim for a month you're obviously not
gonna see any results but you go to the
gym for a year that's when you'll really
see the results or and that's the
compound effect that's because you've
been doing it for a certain amount of
time overtime yeah you know so that's at
me everything wrestling's clearly stands
for that well that's a positive side of
it and then the negative side of is like
obviously you go to McDonald's every day
like for a month you're not gonna see
much of a difference but you go keep
doing that for like six months right you
know you're gonna start having like
heart burns and you know start seeing a
little extra weight on you yeah they're
just little things like that so with I
if you know you constantly do the exact
opposite like the gym whatever it is you
get up and you do your excellence you
earn your excellence thirty days later
you're gonna be better off and just
sitting around exact gunnels and then
not only what I took from that book too
is like it talks about like there's a
section in there where it's like 80% of
people don't pick up a book after high
school and that like that sparked in my
mind and I was like whoa I'm like I
don't want to be that person and then it
also goes on about say anything let's
just say you read ten books a day for a
whole year what's your mindset gonna be
like after that maybe a genius right
yeah pretty much you're obviously going
to be thinking and seeing the world in a
different perspective
I mean books have have a way of
profoundly especially when they're at
such a monumental like like it seems
like all the the things in your life
just led up to that moment in some sense
right so obviously that book is super
profound to you but looks man like I
don't I don't sit down and watch a show
on Netflix or watched an episode of
Parks and Rec for the 17th time
like well that was profound that just
changed the that dis altered the course
of my life the books man when you finish
a good book there's so many nowadays
that I'm just like wow I think
differently now the next few days of my
life I'm walking around a little
differently yeah and I think that's
beautiful like the search for like a
novel thought search for likes a new way
of thinking books are super important
anybody who hasn't picked up a book in a
couple of years if you need reminded man
that you got two guys right here that
are
[__] advocates so you read that book and
that definitely stood out to you the
compound just just working hard
diligently continually exactly and that
like started my journey and continuing
to grow my mind and growing myself as a
person because after that I started you
know learning more about different
philosophies and the way people are
doing things and why people are doing
certain things
that's how after that I started to
realize like I want my designs to have
meaning and you know tell a story right
cuz this is what's making us who we are
you know we are who we are because our
designs speak for themselves you know
it's like you don't go to any other
store and you get a story behind what
you're buying you know you're just going
into the store because you think the
company's cool and everyone's wearing
this stuff right you know we want to be
the company that tells a story or
teaches you something and that's the
thing we're not trying to tell people
what to think or how to think I'm just
trying to plant seeds into their minds
just how in the past people have planted
seeds into my mind so that I can
continue to grow into who I want to be
one day yeah you know and it starts now
because it's the ripple effect my main
target is like the youth the youth has a
big problem of not being conscious of
actually being you yeah they're just
roaming around the world
yeah we're just roaming not even just
the youth it's everyone you know yeah
but I feel like you have it myself man
yeah same you know step test to like
slow down now and be like dang yeah
what's actually going on here you know
because one day you know you'll be 40
years old and you'd be like what have I
been doing yeah well no I did I just
care about exactly I cared about for 40
years you know you want to you want to
be able to like when better when you're
40 like you're gonna be able to say like
man I I'm glad that I that I followed
that seed that was planted my mom you
know like I that I cared about the
correct things I feel like you and you
know I don't see it for every few months
we'll run into each other or meet up and
it's every time you're always like
working on something else plant new
seeds it's good dude you're always
keeping this momentum I feel like when
you're 40 or the things you're gonna say
about I'm gonna be important well it's
the thing like I looked at myself when
I'm 40 now
and that's how you prevent getting to 40
and being like what have I been doing
yeah because you got to think about your
40 year old self now yeah it starts now
because if you're not thinking about him
yeah you know when you meet him yeah we
meet and you're gonna be like damn who
is this guy yeah you don't want to be
that guy yeah you don't just want to be
a bum who hasn't done doing stuff like
well I did watch every every single
episode on Netflix I did too that
throughout my life exactly
I feel like another stepping stone to
like getting to where I am today to was
like I love all my friends but I
realized hanging out with a lot of my
friends like I was just wasting time
and that's when I knew I was different
you know because we'd be sitting there
like playing video games watching TV and
then I just be like I'm literally
wasting time here right my mind was just
going and going and I'm like I need to
go do something I'm like I'm not being
creative I'm like I'm just slacking I'm
like this is not part of my journey
right in any sense that you know it and
that's the thing as a lot of us I think
kind of sit there and still play video
games because we're like no no this is
this is fine but if dude if you've got
something that's screaming at you from
within you got it you gotta be leashed
it but so it's a crazy thing about that
with friends is you know of course there
is friends that just they're gonna fall
by the wayside they're not kind
understand they're gonna be like bro
like you don't hit me up like you're not
a good friend whatever whatever but for
the most part for me anyway as I have
you know in in my different areas that
I've jumped out and been like I'm gonna
be creative or like I'm gonna fall off
the grid for a couple months or I'm
gonna not be able to play video games or
have a beer I'm doing these things me
and my friends like if you just tell
them the honest truth they believe in
you so much that they're like of course
I wouldn't expect anything less you're
so nervous of like breaking free from
your friends all the time because you
think they're gonna hate your guts but
if you just talk to them they're like
bro if court how can I help you
creatively and that's that's another
true whole thing yeah I mean and I feel
like as you get older it's like once you
just have those face-to-face
conversations with a lot of you know
your true homies they're like bro like
why don't you say this sooner let's [__]
this video game let's throw it off the
bridge let's get your company going
I feel like you've had quite a few
friends around you that know I've
noticed a lot of them like that so super
thankful for all you who are listening
much love and yeah my boys and girls
yeah man said work so right now just
kind of channeling it back we're sitting
in your Longview location how long is
this location been open we're coming up
on a neat a year now that's great the
24th I believe will be the 1 year of
being here of being here Longview I
thought it was longer than that
no we opened up our Vancouver location
first oh he did we're on your number two
for Vancouver and you just upgraded your
Vancouver store - yeah that's a bigger
bigger location yeah we just got into a
bigger spot downstairs in the mall we're
still in the same mall but you just got
a bigger spot it's three times the size
and right in the middle of the mall so
there's way more foot traffic and it'll
allow us to get our message in front of
that much more people yeah
holiday season is right around the
corner and the malls get poppin so yeah
exactly I mean it is cool like more
people in your guyses store cuz that's
always the thing that I noticed like
I've done a couple like gigs with you
guys and just standing in the corner
being in the backroom like hearing you
guys talk to your customers it's always
great cuz it's like the more people that
you can get um
you or Andre or whoever out in front
like telling them the story of I
clothing tell you I'm like hey here's
here's what we represent we're not
trying to be like a typical clothing
company no just we're trying to just out
where they represent what's good you
know and once you get you guys in front
of people the more people you get in
front of spreads a message of I and it's
it's great if you like it's a ripple
effect so that's the thing like people
see how passionate we are about what
we're doing that they get inspired and
then they want to go share that with
everyone
absolutely you know and that's the best
part when people come into our store and
they're like because first thing we ask
all our could well first how it starts
is people come in and we're like how are
you doing and they're like oh I'm good
you know that's the typical I'm good I
sell them something yeah or they were
like oh I'm just looking and then
they're like how are some of them are
like how are you and we're like it's a
great day to be alive absolutely and
that's the icebreaker people like whoa I
never use that I was expecting oh oh I'm
good too you know I'm not afraid to be
outwardly happy exactly welcome to a
clothing exactly and some people like
better than alternative
damn right I'm like I like and that's
the thing we're like we like living you
know we don't know what death is like
but I like living and we're gonna make
the most of what we're doing while we're
alive catch on to people to like it
sometimes people come into a clothing
store with a certain mindset of whatever
like me me for example I you know I'm
kind of naturally a more introverted
person I actually like to go into stores
and headphones on the stuff but if I do
notice that the employee is going to God
their way it's like talk to me and yeah
you know they're like or I'll take my
headphones out and talk to them and
sometimes buy them just being outwardly
exuberant it'll pull me out of my
introvert like oh let's just keep my
headphones in sir Mulligan it's all
about that connection you know you want
to make a connection right away and
that's something we really focus on
because like I said earlier it's like
we're not trying to sell you anything
we're just trying to share our messages
and our story with you and hopefully
it's a certain part of you though when
you leave you're like wow like that
that's crazy like yeah two dudes you
know or in their 20s and they already
got stores and they have such a powerful
message like this in they used to sell
beautiful they used to they started out
doodling in high school and selling out
of their trunk it outdoor raves to kids
literally and those are pretty wild
times that's the thing yeah let's go
back to starting out of the trunk of my
car cuz I didn't really go to that yeah
they don't really talk about it people
got to know okay so let's go before so
we're sitting in the store now does a
great online eye clothing check them out
and all that stuff but let's track back
a little bit farther I mean so what I
would do
as a DJ and like an event planner in the
area and I would I would I would get
together with a couple other people yeah
I remember those days
yeah yes some shows outside we do big
sound systems so those few hundred
people we had like upwards of 500 people
sometimes but it'd be very renegade
style like directions the day of but
like even you were like alright there's
gonna be a lot of people here this is
the crowd that I need so you would roll
up with your with your shirts in the
trunk and your cell at the store so
let's talk about that
so yeah the way that it started was when
I came out with my first design I was
super excited I was like dope you know I
got these shirts I got to get rid of
them now you know what good Amana people
need me in high school so I thought like
since I knew a lot of people I was gonna
get a lot of support right away right
but that wasn't the case it took me
about six months to get rid of those 24
t shirts yeah so like like thinking
you're gonna be a millionaire yeah I was
like oh dude I'm gonna sling these real
quick and then gave away seven yeah
exactly yeah sometimes you got to do
what you got to do especially at the
beginning you know get the name going so
what I did was started messaging
hundreds of people like on facebook
Messenger mm-hmm and be like hey I just
started a clothing company this is like
the first design let me know if you're
interested you know and then you'd
obvious get people that would just read
it and ignore you or you'd get the be
like oh I'm good but then you'd get the
ones that'd be like dude that's so cool
like yeah I want one give me this size
so I'd be like okay meet me in the
Walmart parking lot it's you just drug
dealers literally literally so I would
go me with this person in the parking
lot be like hey I got your shirt
Boulevard they give me the money I take
that you know I'd give him the shirt
right and I'd be like all right cool
sell done kappa dev there was this one
time the i'll never forget this moment
but we were at the Safeway parking lot
right by like the gas station and i did
this deal with this person and this
older guy was like hey i saw that and i
was like what
i'm like i'm selling shirts he's and
then he walks over he's like
what exactly are you selling and I pop
open my trunk I'm like shirts
I got mediums yeah he's like oh that's
pretty cool I'm like yeah I'm like this
is all legal I'm like I'm not selling
drugs or anything like oh no he's like I
wasn't thinking that I'm like okay yeah
yeah then why'd you then why'd you say
that
yeah whatever he he backtracked on it so
they jump from selling out of your trunk
to your light like like how long did you
sell shirts out of your trunk for I
clinco like I said probably like a year
yeah I mean and then I obviously started
a website as well as soon as I started
the thing and I taught myself all of
that too you know I just go to youtube
be like oh how do you do this right you
know so that's the thing about nowadays
you know we have the internet we have
YouTube we have Google and all these
great things are great teachers and
mentors you know that's the thing
mentors is the best way you can learn
because you learn from their mistakes
and that's why I read books that's why I
listen to podcasts absolutely that's why
I can look up people on YouTube and
listen to what they have to say you know
because even if they're not there
physically they're still teaching you
something and putting something into
your mind so that you can start thinking
in a different way so that you can solve
a problem that you're stuck on exactly
that's why we listen to those things
yeah always
always learning man like whatever you do
even if you're asking like if you're it
so if you're in the moment right now and
you're you're at that time we are
selling shirts out of your trunk but
it's like I know that this has 10-year
20-year vision like I have something
real here exactly that's due to also
what you should be doing is work on your
business but also improving your mindset
working on reading books at all the time
those audiobooks those podcasts like
there's so many so many out there so
anything you want to know you could just
google it yeah no doubt because that's
the thing if you're not learnt if you're
not learning and growing you're dying
never stop there's no there's no
in-between absolutely you know and then
yeah never stopped Gunn we actually have
a very symbolic design that I came up
with about this was like two years into
the company and we call it the forever
green jury yeah I mean that yeah so the
top of the tree the
top of the designs a tree and then the
bottom of it is a raindrop yeah oh is
that so it's a look at that happen okay
so when you got right now I forgot I was
wearing this one yeah represent always
but yeah I call that the foreverGreen
tree so the tree represents your mind
and the raindrop represents your thought
so as long as you continue to feed your
mind good thoughts you be forever mean
just like the trees then the nun on the
back of any of the t-shirts it's got the
never stopped going down the spine
because it's a symbol of everlasting
growth the raindrop will constantly feed
the trees that it can grow forever but
same thing goes with your mind you
continue to put the right things into
your mind you'll continue to grow into
the person each year so I'll be coming
one day absolutely so like I said try to
be more than just ink on clothes yeah
and you definitely are it's it's so cool
man it's cool I'm really glad that that
you know I thought we've been friends
for a long time so it's cool just watch
it grow in that aspect but it's just
cool to see what agents for the
community yeah dude it's cool to like
link back up in different ways it's very
exciting to think you know what's what's
in ten years what's what you know we're
having this podcast whatever like what's
that going to be in ten years like we
did go excited DJing shirts out of your
trunk last I have like two decent
microphones and you know we've upgraded
so what so what's uh what's the plan for
a guy clothing I mean like like what
where do you see yourself what do you
want to take forward into the future
with I you know not necessarily like
business model but like like what do you
want to keep continue pushing for i
clothing so like the vision that I have
for I is you know I want to have a
thousand stores one day yeah absolutely
I want it to be worldwide so that's a
thing with each location I want people
to come into our store because I want
this our items to be a collectible item
you know so with G with each location
we'll have different stories we'll have
different messages based off of the
region that we're in and the culture
that we're in you know let's just say we
opened up a store in Hawaii like
obviously in that story you won't have
like the all good in the hood
Rena's near stuff that represent the
northwest mm-hmm we would have designs
based off of the culture of where we're
at oh right go that way when you travel
you're like dude I know there's a
nightclub in here like I want to go see
what they have there there's a place
here that represents what this what the
what the beauty in this place is all
about exactly you're almost mining for
the realness of places and sprouting a
story about it exactly
and that's the that's a vision behind
what we want to do and then obviously we
want to get into more media stuff we
want to be like the I media part of you
know the company of court and with that
like the vision behind that it's like I
want to interview people and you know
interview businesses around there you
interview people who like we all want
anything are you saying that you want to
start your own podcast yeah eventually
you guys here to hear there's gonna be
high closing podcasts yeah stay on the
lookout for it not people gonna be
excited they're gonna bug the [__] out
of you better but yeah so like I want to
be able to interview people like
restaurants and stuff so absol make like
a five minute video that says top five
places to eat in Hawaii or whatever part
of why you know we're at or Arizona or
like let's just say top five places and
Phoenix to eat top five places in
Phoenix to I know we just changed the
state Phoenix and I knew no more I guess
I just know more yeah cities and pheenoh
that's that's so important though you're
you're finding the community within you
know what we live in a world of
connection where we're always trying to
connect in the internet week we can
connect but now we can also we can
connect but also mine the communities
and connect the communities because a
lot of times just knowing about each
other it's sort of like really
experiencing the the community the the
reasons the the the deep down that the
the water yeah it gives it birth you
know the seeds yeah of each place so
that's cool that your that your journey
is to pull that out of different places
around the X it's about uniting together
that's what we're about and even in our
stores we carry other local brands in
our stores you know that eyes on you
section so we have giving recognition
people who are out there doing their
thing too you know and then I like to
say this is you know it's like we're not
trying to be better than anyone around
us we're just trying to be the better
version of ourselves you know so we can
continue to grow with our community
because what's the whole point of
bringing someone down and saying like oh
I'm better than or even having the
mindset of I'm better than ya or I'm
trying to win I've always hated that
like even in high school like there was
those kids who thought they were better
than you and those are the kids that I
wanted to be like oh yeah you think
you're better than me wait till you see
who I become one day right and they were
my fuel went out and the sardine ages of
I exactly you know like oh like oh I
really dislike you guys you know yeah
they're the ones that fueled me to
become Who I am today yeah bro you just
gotta ignore him and just like that's
the thing if you know when you're when
you're a kid in the world is telling you
like that you're you're not doing what
you're not doing it right you're not on
my level yeah like it's like man I'm not
failing just I'm not doing what you're
doing you've got to really know in your
heart like man this this thing that I'm
working on it feels like something real
like and you got to keep just mining
that and just keep whatever you guys
think that's cool we'll see you in 10
years buddy see you later like don't
mind do you dream big yeah and another
thing about failing you know that's all
part of the journey you have to fail to
continue to grow because how are you
gonna learn you know and how you grow is
by learning well and you've had plenty
of failures and probably plenty of times
we're like I mean even the beginning I
feel like it probably probably be like
oh we just poured all our money into
these shirts you just said he went six
months without selling 24 shirts oh yeah
luckily I had no overhead and I had
actually I didn't have a job then but
yeah luckily I had no overhead but now
you know that as you get older man the
bigger the biskits the more stores like
you got employees you've got things that
are that are counting on you you know
and so but you've you've built the the
detergent for that you've built like
you're you you're tough now you know
yeah you've done the time well that's
the thing another one of our designs as
meaning is the diamond so the reason I
chose to go with and it's one of it's
part of our banner logo which is like
the main logo that
started with right right it took me like
four times to find the main logo so I
started with like this weird pirate face
looking thing and then I started with
like a lowercase I with an eyeball then
I made a diamond of some sort and then I
upgraded the diamond to the diamond we
have today yeah so the reason I went
with the diamond is because for a
diamond to become a diamond it starts
off as coal and it goes under a lot of
heat and pressure to become the diamond
we as human beings are that coal you
know absolutely we don't start being
tough you know if we go under a lot of
pressure stress problems but for us to
become the diamond we have to overlook
those things and overcome them to become
the diamond yeah but we have to have
faith in being the diamond that diamond
is after the coal yep and not only that
it's like it takes a lot of hard work to
get to a diamond it takes a lot of hard
work to get to your goals and dreams and
then the reason I put the eye in the
center of the diamond is because you
have to have a vision if you don't have
a vision you'll be lost
you hop from one thing to another and
then ten years down the road you're
looking back like dang thought that
degree was gonna help me out or dang I
thought that job was gonna secure me now
you know you're restarting and you don't
know what to do because you didn't set
yourself up for the hard times that
we're gonna come yeah there's always
going to be hard times regardless what
path you choose to take so prepare for
that and you know see it before it
happens accept it yeah visualize it know
that it's actually can come true that
can either be real and and you don't
really know like you can never prep
yourself to be like oh as soon as all
these problems come up I'm gonna know
exactly how to handle them because you
never know how to handle problems man it
comes up and you're like well this sucks
this is why it's a problem because I
don't know how to handle it right
exactly so the most you can do is just
keep your head down but like just have
faith in in the outcome and like know
that I'm still gonna keep chugging away
at this thing I know that this is just a
bump in the road this isn't the end like
let's think about when I'm 40 let's
think about in 10 years you got to keep
you know be in the present and really
you know enjoy what you're doing but
also find a way to keep your head down
and keep chugging forward yeah man it's
it's been it's been really good we're
gonna have to have a lot more of these
podcasts I feel like you're right you
get you yeah I've been up to the
the studio in a well so you gotta kind
of check that out too we'll get Aundre
on here as well yeah we gotta get andres
mine up in here yeah i mean it's on a
different level yeah you know he's
helped me become Who I am today too
smart he knows shout-out to that guy I
mean we can get him on here do it oh
definitely when I want to have the one
on the house I think that's a good idea
yeah I be able to pick his mind yeah
he's a smart guy and do it and walk it
and we're out you know we're all still
learning books and where else we're also
reading books we're all still learning
adapting I want this podcast as well as
I'm sure you want yours to be as well
right definitely just beneficial so it's
like oh I just watched this podcast and
now there's a couple more books that I
know I could read so when what hey what
was that book one more time that slide
edge by Jeff Wilson it's 9:00 at yeah
and that was the one that it kind of
sets you off it seemed like when that
woke me up woke you up yeah yeah they're
really beautiful well Betty oh man I'm
really hyped I got to sit down and and
we got to talk a little bit about like
the birth of I there's always way more
to talk about but we'll get more into
that and once you get your podcast go
because now I'm gonna be pushy about
that with you get your podcast going is
there anything else that you want to
like round out you know like say to the
world anymore like one little message or
anything like that
yeah I think the best thing that you can
do is just do you and not really care of
what other people think of you but I
also realize that your journeys gonna be
tough and the sooner you find out or
realize that your journey journey is
gonna be tough it'll help you get
through the bumps because every day is a
battle yeah you know not every day is
easy you know I have two stores now and
like it's never been harder in my life
and I stress every day and you know it's
like I'm just like any other person you
know I'm not a superhuman or I'm knowing
that special yeah I just knew what I
wanted and I pursued it so if you know
what you want and deep down it's telling
you like hey you need to do this then go
do it regardless what anyone else thinks
you know I like one thing that I heard
from gay like your 20s is your years of
whenever so go to try [__] out try it
out go see what you can do and fill as
many times as you can but don't bring
yourself down because you're failing
yeah something that I've had to overcome
recently you know like so don't bring
yourself down yeah continue to feed your
mind good things and continue to grow
because that's how you get yourself out
of your funk dude yeah I mean in that
thing that if you just keep persevering
through it I mean it in when you do it
the wonderful thing is when you do it
you get permission to other people to do
it just like all these things I gave
permission like in the beginning for you
in high school it's like these kids had
a clothing company you're like oh shoot
we can do that travis pastrana like
someone does a backflip and all sudden
two weeks later everybody else is doing
the back exactly you know you give
people permission and better by you
outwardly living yourself you pushing I
clothing like to your heart's content
like you use it's great you're really
inspiring a ton of people man like
whether whether you know it how much or
not like you really aren't spying a ton
of people from our community now you're
reaching out to other communities I'm
super pumped to see where it goes in the
next 10 20 50 years whatever bro thanks
Jake yeah I really appreciate you you
know bringing me on on this and being
able to spread my messages with out
throughout your community so absolutely
man there'll be plenty more so yeah well
that we'll call it on that and we'll be
back with with Roberto Gonzales sometime
in the near future
sweet hey guys it's Jake
I hope you enjoyed that podcast I'll be
coming out with a few more of these in
the coming months and hopefully as it
picks up momentum there'll be more
releases more broad chapters a few
different ideas that I'm working on that
that'll be enrolled in the coming months
I just wanted to start posting these
before they're fully polished before
they're fully perfected
I know sometimes there's maybe like a
mic nudge or the logos aren't fit
perfectly or you know I don't have an
elegant in intro yeah these are all
things that I want to eventually get but
I do have a perfection issue had time so
I just really wanted to get these out so
anyway
hope you enjoyed the podcast and I just
wanted to say that I really appreciate
you guys the support and you'll be
expecting more if you enjoyed these
please maybe just just share it with
somebody or write write in the comments
if you have any way that I can improve
or if you have any questions that you
think maybe I could answer I'd love to
talk about that so just drop it in in
the comments there otherwise if you're
using an app YouTube Spotify whatever
that autoplay is to the next thing just
just be conscious of your day today if
you don't have all day to be spending on
your phone or listening to stuff and
watching stuff maybe it's better that
you get outside today so just be
conscious of that be healthy peace out
we'll see you next podcast
you